question_data = [
    {"question": "A slug's blood is green.", "correct_answer": "True"},
    {"question": "The loudest animal is the African Elephant.", "correct_answer": "False"},
    {"question": "Approximately one quarter of human bones are in the feet.", "correct_answer": "True"},
    {"question": "The total surface area of a human lungs is the size of a football pitch.", "correct_answer": "True"},
    {"question": "In West Virginia, USA, if you accidentally hit an animal with your car, "
                 "you are free to take it home to eat.", "correct_answer": "True"},
    {"question": "In London, UK, if you happen to die in the House of Parliament, you are entitled to a state funeral.",
     "correct_answer": "False"},
    {"question": "It is illegal to pee in the Ocean in Portugal.", "correct_answer": "True"},
    {"question": "You can lead a cow down stairs but not up stairs.", "correct_answer": "False"},
    {"question": "Google was originally called 'Backrub'.", "correct_answer": "True"},
    {"question": "Buzz Aldrin's mother's maiden name was 'Moon'.", "correct_answer": "True"},
    {"question": "No piece of square dry paper can be folded in half more than 7 times.", "correct_answer": "False"},
    {"question": "A few ounces of chocolate can to kill a small dog.", "correct_answer": "True"},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Matt Damon played an astronaut stranded on an extraterrestrial planet in both "
                 "of the movies Interstellar and The Martian.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Politics", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "There was a satirical candidate named &quot;Deez Nuts&quot; running in "
                 "the 2016 US presidential elections.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Science: Gadgets", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The communication protocol NFC stands for Near-Field Control.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Salt is 100% composed of Sodium.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "History", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Former United States Presidents John Adams and Thomas Jefferson died within hours of each other.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In Alfred Hitchcock&#039;s film &#039;Psycho&#039; it is said he used chocolate "
                 "syrup to simulate the blood in the famous shower scene from ",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Television", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In Battlestar Galactica (2004), Cylons were created by man as cybernetic workers and soldiers.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Valve&#039;s &quot;Portal&quot; and &quot;Half-Life&quot; "
                 "franchises exist within the same in-game universe.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Scotland voted to become an independent country during the referendum from September 2014.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Psychology is the science of behavior and mind.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}
]
